<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gsoc on A weblog of sorts</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/gsoc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gsoc on A weblog of sorts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 21:59:38 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/gsoc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC VisPy - Update #3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-vispy---update-#3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 21:59:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-vispy---update-#3/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the next update, slightly delayed because of college.
SceneGraph is merged The massive SceneGraph PR that was open all this while has been merged into vispy master, bringing closure to that beast. That&amp;rsquo;s part 1 of my GSoC project officially complete!
All of the other changes by me reference a single pull request.
Borders The colorbar had code to render pixel-width borders, that needed to be adapted for a generic case So, the ColorBarVisual was split again, yielding a BorderVisual that&amp;rsquo;s used to draw borders in other parts of VisPy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC VisPy Week 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-vispy-week-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 21:59:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-vispy-week-6/</guid>
      <description>As usual, here&amp;rsquo;s the update for week 6. Let&amp;rsquo;s get down to it!
SceneGraph Overhaul The fabled PR is yet to be closed, but we have everything we need for it to be merged. There were 2 remaining (outstanding) bugs related to the Scenegraph - both stemming from the fact that not all uniforms that were being sent to the shader were being used correctly. One of these belonged to the MeshVisual, a Visual that I had ported, so tracking this down was relatively easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gsoc Vispy Week 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-vispy-week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 02:37:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-vispy-week-5/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this blogpost since we&amp;rsquo;ve come close to hitting a milestone in Vispy&amp;rsquo;s progress - the scenegraph changes are getting merged! So, now, I can move on to phase 2 - building the plotting infrastructure that Vispy needs.
Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve moved the blog from using handrolled html/css/js to Hugo + a standard theme. While not as fun, this is definitely more maintainable, I&amp;rsquo;ve got to admit.
Most of the work for the Scenegraph update is done now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gsoc Update - Weeks 3 &amp; 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-update---weeks-3--4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-update---weeks-3--4/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sitting at home with the flu and a runny nose, so this is as good a time as any to write another blog post!
I managed to get a decent amount of work done over the past two weeks. I think I can start working on plotting from next week, since most of the Scenegraph update I talked about last time is done. What&amp;rsquo;s left is a polish and performance improvements, which will be done iteratively, and (I&amp;rsquo;m hoping) in parallel with the plotting API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gsoc Update - Weeks 1 &amp; 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-update---weeks-1--2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-update---weeks-1--2/</guid>
      <description>The first two weeks of GSoC has gone by, and it&amp;rsquo;s time for another blog post! It&amp;rsquo;s been exciting so far, to work on VisPy and figure out what needs to be done, and how I need to approach it.
A high level overview of these two weeks was basically figuring out where everything should fit in properly, and gently getting everything into shape.
SceneGraph and Plotting We&amp;rsquo;re waiting on a huge pull request to pass through - this one rewrites the entire Scenegraph system in VisPy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gsoc Proposal for Vispy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-proposal-for-vispy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/gsoc-proposal-for-vispy/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The aim of the project is to improve VisPy, a rendering and plotting library for Python. This can be divided into three broad sub-task * Port interesting examples from other graphics libraries like Glumpy to VisPy * Bring high-level plotting constructs to VisPy. * Improve performance by implementing batching (called collections)
Personal Details  Name: Siddharth Bhat Email: siddu.druid@gmail.com IRC nick: bollu Telephone: +91 9008765043 Other contact methods: Skype - druidofdclaw Country of residence: India Timezone: IST (GMT +5:30) Primary language: English  Project Proposal Port Examples The aim of porting examples is to be able to show a clear differential between the way VisPy handles OpenGL versus other libraries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>